export const questions = [
    {
        country:"canada",
        qlist:[
            {
              question: "What is the age range for eligibility for the International Experience Canada (IEC) program?",
              answer: "The age range for eligibility for the International Experience Canada (IEC) program is 18-35 years old (or 18-30 for some countries)."
            },
            {
              question: "What type of work permit is available under the Working Holiday category of the IEC program?",
              answer: "An open work permit that allows participants to work for almost any employer in Canada."
            },
            {
              question: "What are the requirements for participants with an open work permit under the Working Holiday category?",
              answer: "There are no restrictions on how long they can work or how many hours they can work."
            },
            {
              question: "What happens if a participant with an open work permit leaves Canada and returns while their work permit is still valid?",
              answer: "The border services officer will re-assess their admissibility each time they enter Canada."
            },
            {
              question: "What type of insurance is required for participants in the IEC program?",
              answer: "Health insurance that covers medical care, hospitalization, and repatriation for their entire stay in Canada."
            },
            {
              question: "Can family members of IEC participants visit or study in Canada?",
              answer: "Yes, family members can apply to visit or study in Canada."
            },
            {
              question: "What are the categories available under the IEC program?",
              answer: "The IEC program has three categories: International Co-op (Internship), Working Holiday, and Young Professionals."
            },
            {
              question: "What is the duration of stay allowed under the IEC program?",
              answer: "Up to 2 years."
            }
          ]
    },
    {
      country:"australia",
      qlist:[
          {
              question: "What is the age limit for a Working Holiday in Australia?",
              answer: "The Australian Working Holiday visa is open to applicants aged between 18 and 30 (18 to 35 in some cases)."
          },
          {
              question: "Where can I find more information about Working Holiday visas in Australia?",
              answer: "Find the most up to date information regarding visas and the Working Holiday Maker program on the Department of Home Affairs website."
          },
          {
              question: "Which Australian Working Holiday visa should I apply for if I hold a passport from the USA?",
              answer: "Apply for the Work and Holiday visa (Subclass 462) if you hold a passport from the USA."
          },
          {
              question: "Can I leave and re-enter Australia during a working holiday?",
              answer: "Yes. You can leave and re-enter Australia any number of times while the visa is valid."
          },
          {
              question: "How long does an Australian Working Holiday visa last?",
              answer: "Your first Working Holiday visa lasts for 12 months. However, there are options to stay for two or even three years on your working holiday."
          },
          {
              question: "What is required to complete the Australian Working Holiday visa application?",
              answer: "Check the Department of Home Affairs website for the latest updates."
          }
      ]
    },
    {
        country:"newzealand",
        qlist:[
            {
              question: 'What is the age limit for participating in the Korea-New Zealand Working Holiday Program?',
              answer: 'The age limit for participating in the Korea-New Zealand Working Holiday Program is 18-30 years old.'
            },
            {
              question: 'Which countries are eligible for the Korea-New Zealand Working Holiday Program?',
              answer: 'Eligible countries for the Korea-New Zealand Working Holiday Program include South Korea and New Zealand.'
            },
            {
              question: 'How can I apply for a Working Holiday Visa in New Zealand?',
              answer: 'Citizens of eligible countries can apply for a Working Holiday Visa in New Zealand by visiting the New Zealand Immigration website.'
            },
            {
              question: 'What is the purpose of the Korea-New Zealand Working Holiday Program?',
              answer: 'The Korea-New Zealand Working Holiday Program allows young people from both countries to experience each other\'s culture while being able to work and travel for up to 12 months.'
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        country:"netherlands",
        qlist:[
            {
              question: "What is the age range for a working holiday in the Netherlands?",
              answer: "18-30 years old"
            },
            {
              question: "What is the main goal of stay for a working holiday in the Netherlands?",
              answer: "Cultural exchange, not paid employment"
            },
            {
              question: "Is incidental work allowed to support the holiday financially in the Netherlands?",
              answer: "Yes"
            },
            {
              question: "How can I get more information about the working holiday policies in the Netherlands?",
              answer: "Visit the official website of the Dutch Immigration and Naturalisation Service (IND) or contact the IND directly."
            },
            {
              question: "What is required to apply for a working holiday residence permit in the Netherlands?",
              answer: "Completed and signed application form, valid passport and copy of the holder page, 2 passport photographs meeting Dutch requirements."
            }
          ]
    },
    {
        country:"poland",
        qlist:[
            {
              question: "What is the main purpose of participation in the Working Holiday Programme?",
              answer: "To holiday, for a period of up to 12 calendar months."
            },
            {
              question: "What is the application fee for a working holiday visa in Poland?",
              answer: "193,590 KRW (approximately 150 EUR)."
            },
            {
              question: "What is the typical processing time for a working holiday visa application in Poland?",
              answer: "15 days, but can take up to 30 days in some cases."
            },
            {
              question: "What is the required amount of funds for the stay in the Republic of Korea?",
              answer: "USD 3,000."
            },
            {
              question: "Where can you apply for a working holiday visa in Poland?",
              answer: "In the Embassy of the Republic of Korea in Warsaw."
            }
          ]
    },
    {
        country:"austria",
        qlist:[
            {
              question: "What are the objectives of the Working Holiday Programme (WHP) in Austria?",
              answer: "The objectives of WHP are to promote young people's understanding of other countries and cultures, gather professional experience abroad, and acquire/improve foreign language skills."
            },
            {
              question: "Which countries have concluded WHP agreements with Austria?",
              answer: "Austria has concluded WHP agreements with Argentina, Australia, Canada, Chile, Hong Kong, Israel, Japan, New Zealand, South Korea, Taiwan, and the United States of America."
            },
            {
              question: "What is the application fee for the WHP in Austria?",
              answer: "The application fee for the WHP is EUR 120 (approximately KRW 150,000)."
            },
            {
              question: "How long does the processing time for WHP applications take?",
              answer: "The processing time for WHP applications can take up to 2 weeks."
            },
            {
              question: "Where can applicants find information on required documents for the WHP in Austria?",
              answer: "Applicants can find information on required documents for the WHP in Austria at https://www.bmeia.gv.at/fileadmin/user_upload/Vertretungen/Seoul/Dokumente/005_Visainformation_SV-D_Working_Holiday__D_K__2024.pdf"
            },
            {
              question: "Where can applicants submit their WHP applications in person?",
              answer: "Applicants must submit their WHP applications in person at the Austrian Embassy in Seoul."
            }
          ]
    },
    {
        country:"germany",
        qlist:[
            {
              question: "What is the age limit for applying for a working holiday visa in Germany?",
              answer: "The age limit for applying for a working holiday visa in Germany is 18-30 years old."
            },
            {
              question: "Can I apply for a working holiday visa in Germany if I have already been to Germany before?",
              answer: "Yes, you can apply for a working holiday visa in Germany even if you have already been to Germany before, but you must explain the purpose of your stay in your motivation letter."
            },
            {
              question: "How long is the working holiday visa in Germany valid for?",
              answer: "The working holiday visa in Germany is valid for a maximum of 12 months."
            },
            {
              question: "Can I work full-time for a year on a working holiday visa in Germany?",
              answer: "No, you cannot work full-time for a year on a working holiday visa in Germany. If you want to work full-time, you need to apply for a work visa."
            },
            {
              question: "How much money do I need to have in my bank account to apply for a working holiday visa in Germany?",
              answer: "You need to have at least 2,000 euros in your bank account to apply for a working holiday visa in Germany."
            },
            {
              question: "Do I need to have health insurance to apply for a working holiday visa in Germany?",
              answer: "Yes, you need to have health insurance that covers you for at least 30,000 euros in Germany, and the insurance must be valid for the entire duration of your stay."
            }
          ]
    },
    {
        country:"argentina",
        qlist:[
            {
              question: "What is the duration of the working holiday visa in Argentina?",
              answer: "The working holiday visa shall be issued for a period of up to twelve (12) months, non-renewable."
            },
            {
              question: "What is the annual quota for the working holiday visa in Argentina?",
              answer: "The annual quota for the working holiday visa is 200 visas."
            },
            {
              question: "What is the minimum amount of funds required for the applicant's maintenance during the initial period of stay in Argentina?",
              answer: "A minimum of US dollars $2,500."
            },
            {
              question: "What is the minimum amount of medical and accident insurance required for the working holiday visa in Argentina?",
              answer: "A minimum of US dollar $30,000, including repatriation of human remains and sanitary repatriation."
            },
            {
              question: "What is the age range for Korean nationals to be eligible for the working holiday visa in Argentina?",
              answer: "Aged between eighteen (18) and thirty (30), both inclusive."
            },
            {
              question: "Can dependent family members accompany the applicant on the working holiday visa in Argentina?",
              answer: "No, unless they get their own visa."
            }
          ]
    },
    {
        country:"united kingdom",
        qlist:[
            {
              question: "What is the required savings for a working holiday in the UK?",
              answer: "£2,530 in savings."
            },
            {
              question: "How long can I stay in the UK on a working holiday visa?",
              answer: "Up to 24 months."
            },
            {
              question: "Can I work as a professional sportsperson on a working holiday visa in the UK?",
              answer: "No, you cannot work as a professional sportsperson."
            },
            {
              question: "Can I extend my working holiday visa in the UK?",
              answer: "If you are from Australia, Canada, or New Zealand, you can extend your visa by one year after the 2-year period ends."
            },
            {
              question: "How much is the application fee for a working holiday visa in the UK?",
              answer: "£298."
            }
          ]
    },
    {
        country:"israel",
        qlist: [
            {
              question: "What is the age requirement for applying for a working holiday visa in Israel?",
              answer: "The applicant must be between 18 and 30 years old."
            },
            {
              question: "What is the minimum amount of money required to be in the applicant's bank account for a working holiday visa in Israel?",
              answer: "The applicant must have at least $3000 in their bank account."
            },
            {
              question: "Is it necessary to submit proof of a job offer when applying for a working holiday visa in Israel?",
              answer: "No, it is not necessary to submit proof of a job offer when applying for a working holiday visa in Israel."
            },
            {
              question: "How long is the working holiday visa in Israel valid for?",
              answer: "The working holiday visa in Israel is valid for 12 months from the date of first entry into Israel."
            },
            {
              question: "Can the working holiday visa in Israel be extended or changed to a different type of visa?",
              answer: "No, the working holiday visa in Israel cannot be extended or changed to a different type of visa."
            },
            {
              question: "How long does it take to process a working holiday visa application in Israel?",
              answer: "The processing time for a working holiday visa application in Israel is at least 4 weeks."
            }
          ]
    },
    {
        country:"belgium",
        qlist:[
            {
              question: 'What is the primary purpose of the stay for working holiday visa holders in Belgium?',
              answer: 'The primary purpose of the stay must be tourism.'
            },
            {
              question: 'How long is the working holiday visa for Belgium valid for?',
              answer: 'The working holiday visa is valid for 1 year.'
            },
            {
              question: 'What is the application fee for the working holiday visa in Belgium?',
              answer: '€270 (approximately 320,000 KRW)'
            },
            {
              question: 'What is the minimum amount of financial resources required for the working holiday program in Belgium?',
              answer: 'At least €2,500'
            },
            {
              question: 'How long does the application process typically take for the working holiday visa in Belgium?',
              answer: 'The application process typically takes 15 days, but may take longer if additional documents are required.'
            }
          ]
    },
    {
        country:"ireland",
        qlist: [
          {
            question: "What is the duration of the Working Holiday Programme in Ireland?",
            answer: "The Working Holiday Programme allows participants to work and live in Ireland for up to 12 months, with the opportunity to extend their stay for an additional 12 months."
          },
          {
            question: "Do participants need to pay a programme fee for the Working Holiday Programme in Ireland?",
            answer: "There are no programme fees associated with the Working Holiday Programme."
          },
          {
            question: "What is the primary language spoken in Ireland for the Working Holiday Programme?",
            answer: "English is the primary language spoken in Ireland, and participants are expected to have a good understanding of English."
          },
          {
            question: "Are participants allowed to work in Ireland during the Working Holiday Programme?",
            answer: "Participants are allowed to work in Ireland, but they must comply with Irish employment laws and regulations."
          },
          {
            question: "Who is responsible for finding accommodation in Ireland for the Working Holiday Programme?",
            answer: "Participants are responsible for finding their own accommodation in Ireland."
          },
          {
            question: "What is the requirement for health insurance for the Working Holiday Programme in Ireland?",
            answer: "Participants are required to have health insurance that covers them for the duration of their stay in Ireland."
          }
        ]
        
    },
    {
        country:"denmark",
        qlist:[
            {
              question: 'What is the age limit for participating in the Korea-Denmark Working Holiday Program?',
              answer: 'The age limit for participating in the Korea-Denmark Working Holiday Program has been adjusted from 18-30 years old to 18-34 years old, effective June 1, 2024.'
            },
            {
              question: 'Which countries are eligible for the Korea-Denmark Working Holiday Program?',
              answer: 'Argentina, Australia, Canada, Chile, Japan, New Zealand, and South Korea are eligible for the Korea-Denmark Working Holiday Program.'
            },
            {
              question: 'How can I apply for a Working Holiday residence permit in Denmark?',
              answer: 'Citizens of eligible countries can click on the provided link to apply for a Working Holiday residence permit in Denmark.'
            },
            {
              question: 'What is the purpose of the Korea-Denmark Working Holiday Program?',
              answer: 'The Korea-Denmark Working Holiday Program allows young people from both countries to work and travel in each other\'s countries.'
            },
            {
              question: 'When did the Korea-Denmark Working Holiday Program start?',
              answer: 'The Korea-Denmark Working Holiday Program has been in operation since 2011.'
            },
            {
              question: 'Where can I find more information on the Working Holiday Program?',
              answer: 'For more information on the Working Holiday Program, you can contact the Embassy of the Republic of Korea in Denmark.'
            }
          ]
    },
    {
      country:"france",
      qlist:[
        {
          question: 'How long is the working holiday visa valid for in France?',
          answer: 'The working holiday visa is valid for one year and may not be extended, unless otherwise stipulated.'
      },
      {
          question: 'What type of visa is required for a working holiday in France?',
          answer: "The work holiday visa is a long-stay visa containing the statement 'vacances travail' (working holiday)."
      },
      {
          question: 'Can the working holiday visa be extended in France?',
          answer: 'The working holiday visa may not be extended, unless otherwise stipulated.'
      },
      {
          question: 'What is the age limit for applying for a working holiday visa in France?',
          answer: 'Applicants must be between 18 and 30 years of age (i.e., until the day before their 31st birthday), except for Argentina, Australia, and Canada, where the maximum age is 35 years (up to the date of 36th birthday).'
      },
      {
          question: 'Is there a limit on the number of hours that can be worked on a working holiday visa in France?',
          answer: 'There is no limit on the number of hours that can be worked on a working holiday visa in France.'
      },
      {
          question: 'Do employers need to apply for a work permit for working holiday visa holders in France?',
          answer: 'No, employers do not need to apply for a work permit for working holiday visa holders in France, but they must report the employment to the French administration.'
      },
      {
          question: 'Are working holiday visa holders eligible for social security benefits in France?',
          answer: 'No, working holiday visa holders are not eligible for social security benefits in France.'
      },
      {
          question: 'Can working holiday visa holders work full-time in France?',
          answer: 'The visa entitles the holder to undertake paid employment on a secondary basis, without prior approval from the French Administration.'
      }
        ]
  }
]